The celebrities you thought you knew. The videos you've never seen.
kid 90 is a documentary film directed by Soleil Moon Frye.
As a teenager in the '90s, Soleil Moon Frye carried
a video camera everywhere she went.
She documented hundreds of hours of footage and then
locked it away for over 20 years.
Self, played by Soleil Moon Frye.
Self, played by David Arquette.
Self, played by Stephen Dorff.
Self, played by Balthazar Getty.
Self, played by Mark-Paul Gosselaar.
Self, played by Brian Austin Green.
Kid 90 is a 2021 American documentary film directed
and produced by Soleil Moon Frye.
The film follows Frye who carried a camera around with her everywhere she went.
Leonardo DiCaprio serves as an executive producer
under his Appian Way Productions banner.
The film explores themes of new york city, suicide,
skateboarding, loss of virginity, magic mushroom.